coolbusinessideas.com 2019-05-02

# CoolBusinessIdeas.com | Privacy Policy

**Privacy and Security**

The privacy and security of our website visitors and newsletter subscribers is our highest priority. We will never offer any information about you to any third party unless we receive your prior consent. CoolBusinessIdeas.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

**Contents**

The basics of our privacy statement  
Personal information that we gather  
Who receives our emails  
What we e-mail  
Unsubscribing  
Unwanted emails  
Spam filtering  
IP Address  
Cookies  
Links  
Notification of changes  
Legal disclaimer  
Contacting Us

**The basis of our privacy statement**

We will not send you unsolicited e-mail (known as SPAM or UCE). We will only send e-mails to those who have affirmatively requested them through our opt-in process. We will never sell or give away your personal information to third parties for purposes of building contact lists, or anything of that nature, without your permission. CoolBusinessIdeas.com stands firmly against any transfer of personal information for reasons of building the contact lists of third parties.

We respect your right to have your email removed from our databases – you may unsubscribe at any time at your sole discretion. We appreciate you subscribing to our newsletter mailing list and using our website. We will not abuse that privilege. CoolBusinessIdeas.com puts a high priority on list accuracy and quality content.

**Personal information that we gather**

Information on general usage and any optional personal details you provide to us will be used to provide you with enhanced features such as customized content, access to special sections on our web sites and so on.

The following are details of the information we collect:

CoolBusinessIdeas.com collects data through registration from our subscribers. Additionally, usage information may be analyzed so that we can judge our system’s performance or to determine whether we should offer customizable features in the future.

Surveys may ask for contact information or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. Contests may require contact information or other demographic/personal information in order to determine your eligibility.

**Who receives our emails**

Only those who subscribe to our mailing list receive our newsletter. We will only send requested emails to registered visitors and members who have opted-in to our e-mail list. To ‘opt-in’ means you have entered your email address and clicked on the ‘submit’ or ‘go’ button. You may opt-in to our mailing list in this location:

**What we e-mail**

To those who specifically request them, we send the CoolBusinessIdeas.com BIZNESS! newsletter. Special promotional mailings from our partners are emailed to those who have specifically requested for them during the newsletter signup process.

**Unsubscribing**

You may at any time choose to unsubscribe to the CoolBusinessIdeas.com newsletter. To unsubscribe, simply click on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of every issue of the  
CoolBusinessIdeas.com newsletter. Your request will be processed immediately. You will be removed from our list and you will not receive future messages from us.

**Unwanted emails**

There are a few possibilities why you were sent an email you do not want:  
-You have forgotten that you signed up for a service.  
-We are following up on a service you once requested.  
-Someone signed you up without your permission.  
We bear no responsibility in such cases.

**Spam filtering**

If you are using spam filtering software, you can enter the following email address into your filtering software’s “white list” to ensure you continue to receive  
CoolBusinessIdeas.com email messages: bizness@CoolBusinessIdeas.com.  
For best results, add our domain, [www.coolbusinessideas.com](https://www.coolbusinessideas.com/), to your email client’s whitelist.

**IP address**

We use your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times, operating system, country of origin, page views, and users sessions for traffic analysis purposes only. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

**Cookies**

CoolBusinessIdeas.com stores non-intrusive cookies on your computer. This is to facilitate the normal operation of our blog. Please note that some of our advertising partners may use cookies to keep track of their advertising campaigns.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. CoolBusinessIdeas.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites. CoolBusinessIdeas.com is not responsible for any content on any linked sites or for any goods or services available from them. CoolBusinessIdeas.com works hard to ensure that the information contained on our web pages is accurate, relevant and of the high quality that our visitors expect.

**Notification of changes**

CoolBusinessIdeas.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. You have the opportunity to opt-out of our mailing list prior to any substantial change to be taken. However, if you have opted out of all communication from CoolBusinessIdeas.com, you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.

**Legal disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

The contents in this website are solely the opinions of the CoolBusinessIdeas.com editors and should not be considered as a form of therapy nor advice. There is no guarantee of validity or accuracy. CoolBusinessIdeas.com assumes no responsibility for injury. If expert assistance or counselling is needed, services of a competent professional should be sought.

CoolBusinessIdeas.com (a) does not make any warranty, express or implied, with respect to the use of the information provided or made available; (b) does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, usefulness or adequacy of any information accessed via CoolBusinessIdeas.com; and, (c) is not responsible for any errors or omissions in the information accessed via CoolBusinessIdeas.com or for the results obtained from the use of such information.

Any specific reference by name, trade name, trademark, or otherwise to any party does not necessarily constitute or imply its endorsement of the use of such information by CoolBusinessIdeas.com.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact us. Our contact details are stated below.

Email: [contact@CoolBusinessIdeas.com](mailto:contact@CoolBusinessIdeas.com)

Web Address: [https://www.CoolBusinessIdeas.com](https://www.coolbusinessideas.com/)

The CoolBusinessIdeas.com website and newsletter are copyright CoolBusinessIdeas.com. All rights reserved.

Other brands or products are trademarks, service marks, registered trademarks or registered service marks of their respective holders. Content of certain posts on the website is posted under fair use policy.
